export let questions=[{"num":"1","question":"1. A task carried out by the OS and hardware to accommodate multiple processes in mainmemory.","ptn1":"a)Memory control","ptn2":"b)Memory management","ptn3":"c)Memorysharing","ptn4":"d)Memoryusage","right":"b","answered":"0","given":""},
{"num":"2","question":"2. An HTML file is a text file containing small markup tags.","ptn1":"a)True","ptn2":"b)False","ptn3":" ","ptn4":" ","right":"a","answered":"0","given":""},
{"num":"3","question":"3. Secondary memory is the long term store for programs and data while main memory holds program and data currently in use. What kind of an organization is this?","ptn1":"a)Physical","ptn2":"b)Logical","ptn3":"c)Structural","ptn4":"d)none of the above","right":"a","answered":"0","given":""},
{"num":"4","question":"4. Memory organization in which users write programs in modules with different characteristics.","ptn1":"a)Physical","ptn2":"b)Logical","ptn3":"c)Structural","ptn4":"d)Simple","right":"b","answered":"0","given":""},
{"num":"5","question":"5. An executing process must be loaded entirely in main memory. What kind of a memory organization is this?","ptn1":"a)Physical","ptn2":"b)Logical","ptn3":"c)Structural","ptn4":"d)Simple","right":"d","answered":"0","given":""},
{"num":"6","question":"6.FTP stands for?","ptn1":"a)File Text Protocol","ptn2":"b)FileTransferProtocol","ptn3":"c)FirmTransferProtocol","ptn4":"d)FileTransplantProtocol","right":"b","answered":"0","given":""},
{"num":"7","question":"7. A set of overlapping divisions in the main memory are called _______","ptn1":"a)Partitions","ptn2":"b)Divisions","ptn3":"c)Blocks","ptn4":"d)Modules","right":"a","answered":"0","given":""},
{"num":"8","question":"8. Any program, no matter how small, occupies an entire partition. This is called ____________","ptn1":"a)fragmentation","ptn2":"b)priorfragmentation","ptn3":"c)internalfragmentation","ptn4":"d)externalfragmentation","right":"c","answered":"0","given":""},
{"num":"9","question":"9. __________ is used to shift processes so they are contiguous and all free memory is in one block.","ptn1":"a)Fragmentation","ptn2":"b)Compaction","ptn3":"c)ExternalFragmentation","ptn4":"d)Division","right":"b","answered":"0","given":""},
{"num":"10","question":"10. _______ searches for smallest block. The fragment left behind is small as possible.","ptn1":"a)best fit","ptn2":"b)first fit","ptn3":"c)next fit","ptn4":"d)last fit","right":"a","answered":"0","given":""}];
